

Marija Popeska

Address: 6335 Vevcani, 6335 Vevcani, Vevcani, North Macedonia

Email address: marija.popeska@gmail.com

Phone number: (+389) 075238389

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/popeskamarija

GitHub: https://github.com/marijapopeska

(o) Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/popeskamarija/

Gender: Female Date of birth: 25/08/1995

Nationality: Macedonian/citizen of the Republic of North Macedonia

ABOUT ME

Master of Architecture and interior designing, after 4 years of experience I transitioned from Architect to UI/UX designer and was completely self-directed because I found many similarities

Architects strive to design functional and aesthetically pleasing spaces in ways that make their users happy and encourage them to keep coming back. Sound familiar to UX? The way I see it — the only difference between architecture and UX design is the medium; -Architecture deals with physical environments and

-UX deals with digital environments.

I found out that my architectural background is an excellent asset, that provides me with plenty of transferable skills, plus the advantage of bringing a different perspective into the field of UX Designing.

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

HTML/ CSS | CSS3 (SCSS) | UI/Ux | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Ilustrator | AutoCAD | Figma

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[09/2014 - 10/2020] Master of Architecture

Faculty of Architecture , Skopje, ss. Cyril and Methodius University

WORK EXPERIENCE

[05/2018 - 10/2018] **Intership**

Artistika Creative Digital Agency UI/UX

[10/2018 - 05/2021] **Architect**

Civil Engineering Institute Macedonia

[05/2021 - 06/2022] **Architect**

Taktik Architecture

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Free Time Hobbies

- Playing Piano ,
- Training Fitness,
- Sketching ,
- 3D Visualizations